theqcamera.com 2014-02-23

# 

## Privacy Policy

The website with URL address www.theqcamera.com/lab ('Website') is owned and   
operated by Q Lifestyle LTD ('theQ').

theQ respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information.   
This Online Privacy Policy applies to the collection, storage, use and dissemination by theQ of your personal information collected through your use of the Website.   
It applies in addition to theQ general privacy policy and if there is any inconsistency between any term of this Online Privacy Policy and theQ general privacy policy, the terms of this Online Privacy Policy prevail to the extent of such inconsistency. 

By using the Website you acknowledge and agree that theQ may collect, store, use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Online Privacy Policy.   
theQ may amend this Online Privacy Policy from time to time and your continued use of the Website following any such amendment is confirmation of your acceptance of the amendments. 

COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

theQ collects personal information about you through your use of the Website for the purpose of enhancing your use of the Website and assisting theQ in providing you with its range of goods and customer services. 

**Personal information you voluntarily give theQ**  
theQ collects personal information you submit through the Website such as your name, phone number, email address and, where applicable, payment details such as your credit card number or bank account details if you make a purchase online or other personal information if you apply for a job online. theQ will never store any of your payment details, the information we collect are handled by WorldPay UK Limited, our Payment Gateway Provider, for the treatment of those details, please refer to WorldPay privacy policy. (Link http://www.worldpay.com/about_us/index.php?page=privacy&c=WW)

**User Submitted Content**  
theQ collects content that you upload directly to the service (e.g. photos). 

**Website information**  
theQ collects information about your tastes and preferences both when you tell theQ what these are and by analysis of customer traffic, including by use of cookies.   
A cookie is a piece of information, which is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. On revisiting the Website, theQ's computer server recognises the cookie, giving theQ information about your last visit. Cookies do not contain personal information and theQ does not use cookies to personally identify you. theQ uses cookies for the sole purpose of managing functional aspects of the Website including its online store's procedures. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent their automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may not be able to use all of the Website's features, including making purchases. 

USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

theQ will use the personal information you submit online for the purpose of supplying you with the service for which you provide the information. 

theQ may use information it collects about you online to personalize your visits to the Website and help develop the design and layout of the Website. 

You hereby consent that theQ may use the information it collects about you online to contact you from time to time to inform you about new goods, services or offers ('Direct Marketing Communication').   
All Direct Marketing Communications will contain theQ' contact details and a statement indicating that you can (and how to) elect at any time not to receive any further Direct Marketing Communications, even if you previously consented to the receipt of such material.   
theQ reserves the right to keep a record of such requests for the sole purpose of ensuring theQ complies with your request. 

You acknowledge that theQ may disclose the information it collects about you online to its related corporate affiliates. theQ contracts out certain functions of its business including marketing, recruitment and archive services to outside organizations. You hereby consent that theQ may disclose your personal information to such contractors and that theQ, its related corporate affiliates and their contractors may use your personal information for the above purposes. 

DISCLAIMER 

theQ will not disclose your personal information to any third party (other than its related bodies corporate or contractors) without your consent in writing, unless otherwise required by law, or unless such disclosure is reasonable necessary in the opinion of theQ to protect its rights or property or to avoid injury to a person. However in the event that theQ sells or otherwise disposes of some or all of its business to another party, theQ reserves the right to transfer your information as part of any assets sold or disposed of. 

The Website may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. You acknowledge that such sites are not operated by theQ.   
Advertisements on the Website and links to or from other sites do not constitute sponsorship, approval or endorsement by theQ of the content, policies, practices or services offered on those advertisements or sites.

EXTERNAL PARTIES WITH WHOM YOU CHOOSE TO SHARE YOUR USER CONTENT

Any of your personally generated content that you choose to share on other websites or platforms may become available to the public. Upon sharing your content on other platforms or websites that content may be re-shared by others. theQ is in no way responsible for content that has been shared publicly or on other websites or platforms.

If you remove content from your personal account that has already been shared on other websites or platforms that content may remain available through the other websites or platforms and is beyond the scope of this privacy statement. In said case, the user assumes all responsibility for content that has been shared as well as any and all damages that may arise out of sharing of content through other services. theQ does not assume any liability associated with content shared through other websites or platforms.

OTHER WEBSITES AND PLATFORMS

The Website and theQ are in no way responsible for the activities, policies and actions of other websites or platforms to which the user has shared content. Any and all content shared to other websites and/or platforms is beyond the scope of this privacy statement.

STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

theQ will use its reasonable endeavors to protect and maintain the security of your personal information and to make the Website as secure as possible against unauthorized access.

IN CASE OF CHANGE OF CONTROL

In the case that theQ sales a portion or the whole of it's assets to another company or organization, your information as collected by theQ may be transferred.

CONTACT US 

If you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy please contact us at [**hello@theqlifestyle.com**](mailto:hello@theqlifestyle.com).
